(Sheldon:)-Hello.
-Hey.
(Leonard:)You guys didn't break up.
(Sheldon:)No. Sorry to disappoint you,
but Amy pointed out
that you we only trying
to manipulate me.
(Amy:)Which you also
figured out by yourself.
(Sheldon:)Which I also figured out by myself.
(Penny:)Well, I'm glad you're still together.
(Sheldon:)Okay, you can stop trying
to make this about our relationship.
(Amy:)-Which is stronger than ever.
-Which is stronger than ever.
(Sheldon:)This is about you
trying to change my environment,
(Sheldon:)which was perfect the way it was.
(Howard:)But it got the way it was
through change.
(Howard:)The spot that you love to sit in,
that no one else can sit in,
(Howard:)only exists because, despite your
objections, I bought this couch.
(Howard:)Me. So explain why that change
was bad and this change was good.
(Penny:)Um....
(Amy:)You don't need to
explain yourself to him.
(Sheldon:)I don't need to explain
myself to you!
(Amy:)You're sick of his nonsense
and ready to move in with me.
Keep the table!
We don't use that space!